Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray?
Nobody knows for sure!
Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and kick away the darkness!
I'm doing this for myself,
and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
Sanji!
Stay focused!
Behind you!
Ya little runt!
Ouch.
Whaaaa?!
Queen-sama's blade
just snapped right off!
He definitely hit him
in the neck, right?
How did he break that sword with his neck?
You're amazing, Sanji!
Armament Haki?
Whatever it was, that's impossible!
You didn't use Haki, did you?
Germa's got some
serious scientific muscle, don't they?
What's the deal with this?!
Your body's fascinating!
I remember what Judge once said
like it was yesterday:
"Give humans exoskeletons!"
"Give them extraordinary
healing abilities!"
"Give them physical strength!"
"And give them
unfeeling hearts of ice!"
I'm so very sorry!
I've served you something
that did not suit your taste, Niji-sama!
Tryin' to leave a mark
on a lady's face, huh?!
No, I...
...don't want to become
one of those heartless monsters!
But you are a monster!
Welcome to this monster world!
Black Light Roast!
Wait a minute, dammit!
What the hell's
happening to my body?!
I need some time to process this!
Think back!
What've I done up 'til now?!
Who the hell are you?!
Sangoro!
Is it because
I transformed into Soba Mask?
No way!
Am I seriously losing who I am?!
Sanji's...
...been acting real funny...
That's one of the Straw Hats!
Queen-san's got him cornered!
He's mumbling something...
This's our chance!
Shoot to kill!
You're done,
Black-Leg Sanji!
yeah!
Got im!
Ya-hoo!
That hurt, ya know!
Whaaaa?!
That's one tooough exoskeleton!
Put on your combat suit!
Show me more
of Germa's science!
I got nothin' to do with those bastards!
Don't lump me in with them!
I'm betting you're a Navy spy.
But in this case,
it doesn't matter...
The real question is,
do you or don't you wanna take down Kaido?
When this battle is over,
the winners're gonna be
on their last legs!
Won't be hard to finish 'em off then!
Whaddya think?
Wanna pal around with us and take everything
for ourselves after all's said and done?
Kaido's army, the rebel army...
Since we're part of neither side,
we don't got reason to be at each other's throats!
I'm amazed...
You really think
I'd trust a coward like you?
You're hardly to be trusted yourself!
I'm telling you this because
I think there's benefits in it for you!
You're not gonna get...
...another opportunity like this!
Why do you laugh?
I took you for the sort
that doesn't laugh much...
You didn't...
You ate a Smile Fruit, didn't you?!
You have the greatest
misfortune, Killer!
Hey, look!
Killer-san!
You guys!
Basil Hawkins!
Kaido's stinkin' lapdog!
How could you betray us?!
Please...!
Don't!
Lay a hand on him
and I'll make sure you regret it!
Killer-san, why won't you
let us help out?!
Your captain is my hostage.
It appears he's fighting
Big Mom now...
A losing prospect for him,
if you ask me.
As it is, there are few fates
that remain available to you.
Killer-san!
So frustrating!
The fire's closing in, too!
We gotta get outta here, and fast!
Master!
We rescued Komachiyo!
Hurry, or the fire's
gonna swallow us!
It's a monster!
A monster of the lower half variety!
Somebody, lend me aid-poo!
Uh?!
Huuuuh?!
Someone, anyone-poooo!
Wait, wait!
What the heck are you doing?!
I require assistance-poo!
That's why I need you to wait!
Who goes there-poo?!
I be Kin'emon-poo!
Calm down!
Just calm down!
He ain't a monster, then?
A human?
That's human?
I seek my allies-poo!
And I'm one of them,
Kin'emon!
It's me!
Usopp!
Unhand me-poo!
There is no time to poose!
Whoa, talk about blood loss!
Are you okay?!
Usopp, he can't hear us!
His ears are on his other half!
Oh, yeah!
But we gotta let him know
it's us, somehow!
Who goes there?!
Identify yourselves-poo!
How is he talking?
His farts.
Guess that's one of
Kin'emon's specialties,
HuhB
Farts!!
What an amazing skill!
Worth a shot...
Boop!
Was that the reverse crescent moon?!
Then you be an ally of mine-poo!
All right!
He got it!
Then, I've a request
to ask of poo...
One of my companions yet breathes,
however faint...
Please, do whatever
you can to aid her!
We're borrowing Hamlet!
You guys take care of Tama!
My goodness!
Everybody needs me!
Thank poo!
I know not who you be,
but you be an ally of mine!
In the left tower on the castle's first floor
lies an entrance to a crawl space!
Leave it to me!
What the hell's up
with this pain?!
Hey, what's wrong with you?!
What's your deal?
Got a migraine...
...Kid?
Dammit!
Let's go, Hera!
Yes, Mama!
Napoleon!
If it's hurting that bad,
how about I rêlieve your head
from your shoulders!
Combine!
Thank me later!
What is your problem?!
You're useless, you know that?!
You're in my way, you quack!
Chambres!
Counter Shock!
Mama!
You'll pay for that!
Stolen Feuer!
Mama-Raid!
A ballsy idiot's head,
or a quack's arm...
Which one do I take first?
Dammit all to hell...
I'm finally going toe-to-toe
with an Empress of the Sea!
If I die here, what was...
...the point of living
the pirate life?!
You crack me up,
Kid!
Eustasser!
You look like you could keel over
without my help!
Stop!
Stop it, Hawkins!
You're pathetic, Killer.
Don't!
This sucks...!
What the hell is
going on with me?!
Let Kid go!
In return...
...you can have...
...my life!
Killer-san!
Once Kid is no more,
life will be easier for you.
The extent of your misery
can be traced back to him.
You don't get it, do you,
Hawkins?
Kid's gonna put
the Four Emperors to shame...
...and become the Pirate King!
Stop it already!
Hunt down the Four Emperors?
Be the Pirate King?
How admirable,
having such grand ambitions!
Don't get in our way, then!
If I'm in your way,
then cut me down with your scythes!
Or you can surrender,
makes no difference to me.
I'll even put in a word
for you with Kaido-san.
Are you asking me to work for Kaido?
That's low, even for you...
Silence!
At any rate, this is a battle
you and your ilk cannot win!
You've seen how
harsh reality is, aye?
Now you know the reasons
behind their lengthy rule of these seas!
I know your animal instincts
are telling you
"There's no way I can win!"
Go ahead, keep barkin'...
You're regretting it, ain't ya?
The choice you made back then.
Come work for me,
and you'll get a warm welcome...
Turn me down, and...
Regretting it 'cause you were scared
of dying in this future,
but here we are, still kicking!
You will soon know which of us
regrets their decision!
Sure, buddy...
Then I think...
I'll just live without regrets!
Sink or swim!
You're just wearing
yourself out!
See you in hell,
you worthless cub!
Two questions for you:
What happens if you take damage...
...but it's got nowhere to go?
What are you on about?!
You know how my powers work!
Kid receives all damage I take...
...as long as his straw doll
is stored within my body!
That so?
Why?!
You severed my arm!
But all damage must...!
Kid...
...has no left arm!
Drat!
I did not foresee this!
So, question number two...
If I take this away,
how many more lives do you have left?
Congratulations!
That's the last one.
The pain's... gone,
just like that?
Straw Man's Cards!
Death, Upright.
The card of destruction!
Guillotine Claws!
The Strawman's been...!
The Strawman won't die!
If it is in the cards,
it will return!
Reveal to us the outcome
of this battle!
The Tower!
Spin & Sonic!
Way to go!
Killer-san!
Hawkins-san!
Straw Man's Cards:
The Tower...
It represents...
"The collapse of the old"...
What's this, now?
All better now, are we...
Kid?
Yeah...
Feels like a load off my shoulders.
Its hidden meaning:
"A new path."
Get goin', partner!
A bit longer...
Endure for just a little bit longer...
Kiku!
I have just made contact
with our allies...
Still...
I could scarcely believe that I was still alive
even after being cleaved in twain!
I suppose when Law-dono cut my body in half,
it was never properly reattached...
A miracle!
Now if only...
If only Kiku can be...
saved... somehow...
Hey...
Hey!
Answer me, Kanjuro!
Can you hear me, Kanjuro?!
It cannot be!
Why do I hear Orochi's voice?
I am certain I beheaded him,
with my own hands!
And Kanjuro is already...!
Hey, Kanjuro!
Yes, Orochi-sama...
Barely breathing,
I see, Kanjuro...
I... I must say that this is...
...the end of my performance...
Aye!
My hat's off to you, sir!
An outstanding performance, it was!
I appreciate your kind words
more than anything...
Kanjuro, do you hear them?!
The cheers for you?!
F-For me?
Kurozumi!
Yet I remain frustrated...
Resentful!
Indeed...
Our ancestors...
...await...
...a spectacular encore!
Paint it for me, Kanjuro!
The Kurozumi Clan's
burning grudge!
Who shall be the winner?!
The deep-seated wrath of
the Kurozumi Clan...
...shall parade through this castle,
and at last!
It shall...
it shall walk unto the abyss,
and the nadir where it reaches an impasse
shall serve as our graveyard!
Bring solace to our spirits,
Kanjuro!
As you wish.
I shall display for you...
...Kurozumi Kanjuro's
final performance!
Kurozumi Mass Suicide:
Swift Finale!
Kazenbo!
We're gonna burn alive!
M... Monster!
Reporting in!
A giant spectre of unknown origin has appeared
on the second floor of the castle interior!
The specter is passing through the walls
like some kind of ghost!
The castle has turned
into an inferno!
It's time, time, time,
time to show me...
...Germa's suuuu-it!
Stupid freakin' lizard...
I'm sick of hearing you
talk about that!
That's it, then...
Time to go, everyone!
This is no time for fighting!
You're right...
Before the flames cut off our retreat!
Allies of the Kozuki...
Rulers of the sea...
Pride goeth...
...before a fall!
Blast Breath!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!